{
    "subject": "resource/Red_Hot_Chili_Peppers",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "The hometown of Red Hot Chili Peppers is United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8785914182662964,
            "question": "Is the United States home to the Red Hot Chili Peppers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8396108150482178,
            "question": "What country is the hometown of the Red Hot Chili Peppers located in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7109530568122864,
            "question": "Is the United States the birthplace of the Red Hot Chili Peppers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6128148436546326,
            "question": "Where are the Red Hot Chili Peppers from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4825400710105896,
            "question": "Where did the Red Hot Chili Peppers form?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39817187190055847,
            "question": "What is the nationality of the Red Hot Chili Peppers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35972538590431213,
            "question": "To which country do the Red Hot Chili Peppers belong musically?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34816494584083557,
            "question": "In what country were the Red Hot Chili Peppers originally based?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3143616020679474,
            "question": "Which nation considers the Red Hot Chili Peppers as its own?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19130273163318634,
            "question": "What is the origin country of the band Red Hot Chili Peppers?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The hometown of Red Hot Chili Peppers is United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9152_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which nation considers the Red Hot Chili Peppers as its own?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9152_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what country were the Red Hot Chili Peppers originally based?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9152_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To which country do the Red Hot Chili Peppers belong musically?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9152_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9152_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9152_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9152_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9152_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9152_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9152_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9152_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9152_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9152_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9152_85.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, here's my evaluation:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nExplanation:\nThe documents mention that Red Hot Chili Peppers are an American rock band formed in Los Angeles, California in 1983. This implies that their hometown is indeed the United States, specifically Los Angeles."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide information about the Red Hot Chili Peppers being an American rock band formed in Los Angeles, California. This supports the statement that their hometown is the United States."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}